{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769644684","data":{"timestamp":" 947769644683"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" aadcf653-8d3f-455f-8dfd-f2edab491a78"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nye..nye.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.56"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nye_we-mmo-nye"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769662483","data":{"timestamp":" 947769662483"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mta_nji-mno-mta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mta"," userResponse":" mta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769667100","data":{"timestamp":" 947769667100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mgu_nje-nja-mgu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mgu"," userResponse":" mgu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769671937","data":{"timestamp":" 947769671937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nde_kwa-mwi-nde"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nde"," userResponse":" nde"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769677946","data":{"timestamp":" 947769677946"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpi_mpi-bwa-cha"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpi"," userResponse":" mpi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769682635","data":{"timestamp":" 947769682635"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_thi_njo-swa-thi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" thi"," userResponse":" thi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769688971","data":{"timestamp":" 947769688971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_bwa-nji-mfa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769694887","data":{"timestamp":" 947769694887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nja_mwo-vya-nja"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769700382","data":{"timestamp":" 947769700382"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mke"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769706519","data":{"timestamp":" 947769706519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_mgo-mke-mki"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769711403","data":{"timestamp":" 947769711403"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ndu_ndu-chi-nyi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ndu"," userResponse":" ndu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769718589","data":{"timestamp":" 947769718589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mzu"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769724365","data":{"timestamp":" 947769724364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e1026b64-8b6e-4c91-85c8-bb77f6880e0d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.76__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mzu_mme-dha-mzu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769734135","data":{"timestamp":" 947769734135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769734372","data":{"timestamp":" 947769734371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769735348","data":{"timestamp":" 947769735348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769736624","data":{"timestamp":" 947769736624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769739492","data":{"timestamp":" 947769739492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769740336","data":{"timestamp":" 947769740335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769740655","data":{"timestamp":" 947769740655"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769743498","data":{"timestamp":" 947769743497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769747535","data":{"timestamp":" 947769747535"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769748546","data":{"timestamp":" 947769748546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769748805","data":{"timestamp":" 947769748805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769749757","data":{"timestamp":" 947769749756"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769752547","data":{"timestamp":" 947769752547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769753583","data":{"timestamp":" 947769753582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769754056","data":{"timestamp":" 947769754056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769758625","data":{"timestamp":" 947769758623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769758729","data":{"timestamp":" 947769758728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" ba3fe03b-c995-436a-8861-aad1d05646be"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769779637","data":{"timestamp":" 947769779637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_bu_ro_ngu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769786306","data":{"timestamp":" 947769786306"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_mku_de_ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769791180","data":{"timestamp":" 947769791179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mku_de_ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769828167","data":{"timestamp":" 947769828167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mku_de_ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769832964","data":{"timestamp":" 947769832964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mku_de_ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769838496","data":{"timestamp":" 947769838496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mku_de_ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769866112","data":{"timestamp":" 947769866111"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 64b0ebea-6f62-477c-9f68-d27e0d917bab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_syl.lc.say.ngu..ngu.noShow..20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_mku_de_ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947769882854","data":{"timestamp":" 947769882854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cc58374a-dce9-4e09-a1ea-df4555014142"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770246380","data":{"timestamp":" 947770246379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-4-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770253677","data":{"timestamp":" 947770253677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770259923","data":{"timestamp":" 947770259923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-7-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770269210","data":{"timestamp":" 947770269210"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_6-2-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770289790","data":{"timestamp":" 947770289790"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_6-7-5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770294228","data":{"timestamp":" 947770294228"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_6-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770300871","data":{"timestamp":" 947770300871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770308290","data":{"timestamp":" 947770308290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770319400","data":{"timestamp":" 947770319399"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770330684","data":{"timestamp":" 947770330684"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770335158","data":{"timestamp":" 947770335158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7a074a1b-55bd-4437-ad29-59793d8ac984"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-9-3"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770369889","data":{"timestamp":" 947770369889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cb206d03-ee88-4eae-8cfd-84c19f4df5de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mchu-be-ngu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770376612","data":{"timestamp":" 947770376612"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cb206d03-ee88-4eae-8cfd-84c19f4df5de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-ti-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770378327","data":{"timestamp":" 947770378327"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cb206d03-ee88-4eae-8cfd-84c19f4df5de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-ti-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770385215","data":{"timestamp":" 947770385215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cb206d03-ee88-4eae-8cfd-84c19f4df5de"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-ti-mchi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770396168","data":{"timestamp":" 947770396168"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cbcfcd7b-3897-448b-98ea-df63efde33c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770396482","data":{"timestamp":" 947770396482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cbcfcd7b-3897-448b-98ea-df63efde33c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770396690","data":{"timestamp":" 947770396690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cbcfcd7b-3897-448b-98ea-df63efde33c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770404393","data":{"timestamp":" 947770404392"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cbcfcd7b-3897-448b-98ea-df63efde33c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770414229","data":{"timestamp":" 947770414229"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" cbcfcd7b-3897-448b-98ea-df63efde33c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_23"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770428585","data":{"timestamp":" 947770428584"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 17f92d92-57a8-4895-9c65-1556c957b91d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_za-je-ngu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770429685","data":{"timestamp":" 947770429685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 17f92d92-57a8-4895-9c65-1556c957b91d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_za-je-ngu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770438348","data":{"timestamp":" 947770438348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 6c35c214-f130-4739-8b7d-5ea004b2b8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770438572","data":{"timestamp":" 947770438572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 6c35c214-f130-4739-8b7d-5ea004b2b8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770438945","data":{"timestamp":" 947770438944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 6c35c214-f130-4739-8b7d-5ea004b2b8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770439064","data":{"timestamp":" 947770439064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 6c35c214-f130-4739-8b7d-5ea004b2b8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770453376","data":{"timestamp":" 947770453375"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 6c35c214-f130-4739-8b7d-5ea004b2b8f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770570341","data":{"timestamp":" 947770570341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 4b13a2bc-8f4a-435f-a785-336b4294786b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770571068","data":{"timestamp":" 947770571067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 4b13a2bc-8f4a-435f-a785-336b4294786b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770590820","data":{"timestamp":" 947770590820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mu-su-ngu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770595845","data":{"timestamp":" 947770595844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mzu-mchu-ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770613597","data":{"timestamp":" 947770613597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-ng'u-hu"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770621710","data":{"timestamp":" 947770621710"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_su-mbu-ngu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770630400","data":{"timestamp":" 947770630400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-ru-ndu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770638834","data":{"timestamp":" 947770638833"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-mju-mfu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770643604","data":{"timestamp":" 947770643603"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-nu-gu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770649987","data":{"timestamp":" 947770649986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-mvu-mgu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770660045","data":{"timestamp":" 947770660045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_nyu-gu-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770666543","data":{"timestamp":" 947770666543"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mchu-ngu-pu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770672424","data":{"timestamp":" 947770672424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" e3e8389e-67ca-4650-839b-e58fec8965eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.58"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mchu-ngu-pu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770682479","data":{"timestamp":" 947770682479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770682703","data":{"timestamp":" 947770682703"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770692052","data":{"timestamp":" 947770692052"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770693329","data":{"timestamp":" 947770693329"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770704276","data":{"timestamp":" 947770704276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770705127","data":{"timestamp":" 947770705127"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770705442","data":{"timestamp":" 947770705442"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770706681","data":{"timestamp":" 947770706681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770710254","data":{"timestamp":" 947770710254"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770711240","data":{"timestamp":" 947770711240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770711494","data":{"timestamp":" 947770711494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770712440","data":{"timestamp":" 947770712439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770740299","data":{"timestamp":" 947770740299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770741332","data":{"timestamp":" 947770741332"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770741807","data":{"timestamp":" 947770741806"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770743796","data":{"timestamp":" 947770743796"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770744023","data":{"timestamp":" 947770744023"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" faa32793-4d41-44cc-8055-fdb58acf41bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770760446","data":{"timestamp":" 947770760445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_ngu-che-ra"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770765614","data":{"timestamp":" 947770765614"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_wo-ngu-me"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770770590","data":{"timestamp":" 947770770589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_nge-ngu-mja"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770837276","data":{"timestamp":" 947770837275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_so-ngu-po"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770853060","data":{"timestamp":" 947770853060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_msi-ngu-hi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770858440","data":{"timestamp":" 947770858440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_nchi-da-ngu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770864938","data":{"timestamp":" 947770864938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mku-do-ngu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770879881","data":{"timestamp":" 947770879881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mwe-ngu-mtu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947770887944","data":{"timestamp":" 947770887944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771006617","data":{"timestamp":" 947771006617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771029327","data":{"timestamp":" 947771029326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771036973","data":{"timestamp":" 947771036973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771052105","data":{"timestamp":" 947771052105"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771162316","data":{"timestamp":" 947771162316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771171459","data":{"timestamp":" 947771171459"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771180801","data":{"timestamp":" 947771180801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771189987","data":{"timestamp":" 947771189987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771202120","data":{"timestamp":" 947771202120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771211562","data":{"timestamp":" 947771211562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771224064","data":{"timestamp":" 947771224064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 67078e9f-9ae6-4bd9-8225-bc863314a012"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ngu..ngu.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.59"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ngu_mte-ri-ngu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771242085","data":{"timestamp":" 947771242085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" db383b62-d980-4a06-9ec4-6667cb7384ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nju"," userResponse":" nju"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771242863","data":{"timestamp":" 947771242862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" db383b62-d980-4a06-9ec4-6667cb7384ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771253381","data":{"timestamp":" 947771253381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" db383b62-d980-4a06-9ec4-6667cb7384ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771271006","data":{"timestamp":" 947771271006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" db383b62-d980-4a06-9ec4-6667cb7384ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771300137","data":{"timestamp":" 947771300134"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" db383b62-d980-4a06-9ec4-6667cb7384ae"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.75__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nju_she-nju-mjo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771310648","data":{"timestamp":" 947771310648"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771310876","data":{"timestamp":" 947771310876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771311848","data":{"timestamp":" 947771311847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771313125","data":{"timestamp":" 947771313125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771316251","data":{"timestamp":" 947771316250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771317097","data":{"timestamp":" 947771317096"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771317423","data":{"timestamp":" 947771317423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771318664","data":{"timestamp":" 947771318663"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771322239","data":{"timestamp":" 947771322239"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771323237","data":{"timestamp":" 947771323237"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771323495","data":{"timestamp":" 947771323495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771324447","data":{"timestamp":" 947771324447"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771327397","data":{"timestamp":" 947771327397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771328437","data":{"timestamp":" 947771328437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771328911","data":{"timestamp":" 947771328910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771329056","data":{"timestamp":" 947771329056"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947771329231","data":{"timestamp":" 947771329231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_162000"," gameId":" 7e5af35b-d46b-4285-ad48-9797aa3a39a6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}